So, let's define the Precision metric as follows.
Vamos definir a métrica da precisão como falsa.
Here is the Confusion matrix of the medical model.
Esta é matriz do modelo médico,
And we've added a red X in the spot that we really want to avoid,
nós colocamos um X vermelho no que queremos evitar,
which is the false negatives.
que são os falsos negativos.
So Precision will be the answer to a question out of
A precisão será a resposta à pergunta:
all the points predicted to be positive,
de todos os pontos tidos como positivos,
how many of them were actually positive?
quantos deles realmente eram positivos?
In this case, the question translates to,
Neste caso, a pergunta é a seguinte:
out of all the patients that we diagnosed as sick,
se todos os pacientes diagnosticados como doentes,
how many were actually sick?
quantos estavam realmente doentes?
So Precision is this column,
A precisão é esta coluna, pois estes são os pacientes
So it is 1000 that were correct divided by 1800,
São os 1.000 corretos divididos por 1.800,
which is the total number of patients diagnosed as sick.
que é o total de pacientes diagnosticados como doentes.
This number is 55.7%.
Temos 55.7%.
It's not a high number because this is not a very precise model.
O valor não é alto, pois o modelo não é preciso.
But again, this is okay because what we're doing is avoiding this red X.
Mas tudo bem, pois estamos evitando o X vermelho.
Now, let's look at the spam e-mail model. What is this Precision?
Vejamos o modelo de e-mail spam.
Now, know that in this model Precision is very important,
A precisão aqui é muito importante,
because the red X that we're avoiding is in this column.
porque o X que estamos evitando está nesta coluna.
The red X is the non-spam emails that were accidentally sent to the spam folder.
Estes são os e-mails erroneamente enviados para a pasta de spam.
So those 30 errors are really bad and we want to avoid them.
30 erros é muita coisa, e nós queremos evitá-los.
So again, Precision says,
A precisão diz que, de todos os e-mails na pasta spam,
how many of them were actually spam?
quantos realmente são spam?
So we have 100, which are correct,
São 100 corretos
divide it by 130,
divididos pelos 130 e-mails
This number is 76.9% which is higher.
Isso é igual a 76.9%, que é mais alto.
This is better, since this model needs high Precision,
Isso é melhor, pois o modelo precisa ser de alta precisão,
so the number better be big.
então o valor precisa ser alto.
Now, let's do an exercise.
Vamos fazer um exercício.
Let's go to our linear model over here.
Vejamos este modelo linear.
What is the Precision of this linear model?
Qual é a precisão deste modelo linear?
Enter your answer below.
Escreva a resposta abaixo.